https://randrlaundryequipment.co.uk/privacy-policy/

R & R Laundry Equipment | Read Our Privacy Policy
MenuHomeAbout UsEquipment For SaleWashing MachinesIroning EquipmentFinishingFolders & FeedersDryersBoiler, Compression And AncillariesNewsContact UsLinkedIn
femdomss.comPrivacy PolicyHomePrivacy Policy
When you use our website, we may collect certain information about you, but we offer our assurance that all actions are in-line with UK and EU laws. We take all steps necessary and within our power to protect your information and privacy.
Data we may collect
In order to improve our services and provide a better experience for our users, we may collect some of your data, such as:
• Your IP address
• The web browser you’ve used to access our website
• Your email address
• Cookies – please see our cookie policy
Data storage
Any data we collected will be stored on our secure servers, but as with any online transmission, we can’t make a 100% guarantee of its complete security – when you submit any personal data on our website, you are accepting this minimal risk to your data.
Sharing your data
We will never pass on any of your details to other websites or organisations.
Contact and communication
Contacting this website and/or its owners is at your own discretion and while every effort has been made to ensure that our email submission form is safe and secure, we advise that using this function is done so at your own risk.
We may use information you’ve submitted to provide you with further information about our products or to answer any query you may have.
In compliance with UK Spam Laws and the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003 subscribers are given the opportunity to unsubscribe from any unwanted communications, such as email newsletters and campaigns, at any time through an automated system. Alternatively, you can contact us and ask us to remove your details.
External Links
We strive to ensure that any links we provide to external websites are safe, relevant and of good quality, but we recommend ‘clicking with caution’. We cannot be held responsible for the content, safety or privacy policy of any external websites and therefore advise that you visit these sites at your own risk.
adultcomics.me
shemalevids.org
incestgames.net
Want to know more? Request A Callback!Request Callback
Privacy Policy | Cookie Policy
T: 01245 500326
E: info@randrlaundryequipment.co.uk
Quick Links
